Pam,give me a garden salad and a grilled fish appetizer.
Pam, 给我一个果园沙拉和一个烤鱼开胃菜.
Right.
好的.
Pam,please turn off that burner.
Pam,请关掉那个炉子.
Got it.
知道了.
And a moussaka special and fetucine Alfredo,
和一个moussaka special和fetucine Alfredo,
no cream.
不要奶油
Hand me those bowls,please.
递给我那些碗, 请.
-What? -What?
-什么? -什么?
I can't give a customer Alfredo sauce with no cream.
我不能给一个客人Alfredo sauce 不含奶油
Fettucine Alfredo: pasta with cream,cheese,pepper...
Fetucine Alfredo: 意大利面带有奶油,奶酪和胡椒粉...
Use milk.
用牛奶(替代)
For Alfredo sauce,I need cream.
对于Alfredo sauce, 我需要奶油.
He doesn't want cream.
他不想要奶油.
He can have a nice spaghetti primavera.
他可以要一份不错的spaghetti primavera.
No cream.
没有奶油.
I'm not going to give him something else.
我才不会给他别的东西的.
And I'm going to put cream in it.
我就要放奶油在它里边.
I am going to put extra cream in it.
我要放额外的奶油在它里边.
Oh.Do you want to give him high cholesterol?
Oh. 你想要给他 高胆固醇(high cholesterol)?
Fine.
You go out and tell him.
你出去告诉他.
He's the man on the left at the middle table.
他是男的 坐在左边 在中型桌.
What am I going to do with you?
(让)我拿你怎么办呢?
It's not me,Jarmusch. I like cream.
不是我, Jarmusch. 我喜欢奶油